Scenic Hudson, Inc. Administrative History Collection
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
The Scenic Hudson, Inc. Administrative History Collection
1960 - 2000
Hudson River Sloop Clearwater, Inc.
NPKMC-221-254
62.25 Linear Feet
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
The Scenic Hudson, Inc. Administrative History Collection documents the development of the environmental group from their landmark achievement of preserving historic Storm King Mountain to their present day efforts of protecting and preserving the environmental integrity and beauty of the Hudson River and its surrounding areas. The collection consists of administrative records and files, newspaper clippings, still photographs, correspondence, Scenic Hudson News and Annual Reports, legal materials, agenda and minutes of meetings, as well as a variety of other printed materials. Also included in the collection are files dealing with such topics as dredging, air pollution, Danskammer, the Marcy-South transmission lines, as well as a variety of other subjects.
Scenic Hudson, Inc. donated The Scenic Hudson, Inc. Administrative History Collection to the Marist College Library in 2003.
There are no restrictions on this collection
Historical Note
In September 1962, the Consolidated Edison Company announced plans to build a pumped storage facility, the largest of its kind in the world, at Storm Kind Mountain near Cornwall, New York. The initial application for license to construct the plant was filed with the Federal Power Commission in January 1963. On November 8, 1963, a small group of concerned citizens met at the home of Carl Carmer and formed the Scenic Hudson Preservation Conference to fight the pumped storage project on the grounds that it posed a threat to the Cornwall water supply and Hudson River fisheries as well as to scenic and historic Storm King Mountain. The case lasted for 17 years. In a negotiated settlement in December 1980, Consolidated Edison agreed to drop the plan for the Storm King facility. In the meantime, Scenic Hudson emerged at the forefront of the environmental movement. Over the past thirty-five years, Scenic Hudson, Inc. has safeguarded over 18,000 acres of irreplaceable landscapes, protected productive farmland, reclaimed and transformed neglected industrial waterfront sites, and purchased strategic properties to revive community centers.
Collection Overview
The Scenic Hudson, Inc. Administrative History Collection contains materials anddocuments pertaining to the development, growth, and accomplishments of Scenic Hudson, Inc. Its contents consist of correspondence, legal papers, subject files, environmental studies, printed materials, clippings, and photographs.
Collection is arranged into twenty-nine series: 1. Background Material, 2. Meetings, 3. Legal Papers, 4. General Correspondence, 5. Printed Material, this series has ten subseries, 6. Events, 7. Maps, 8. Subject Files, 9. Adjudicatory Hearings, 10. Alsen Coal, 11. Danskammer Coal, 12. Federal Power Commission, 13. Harvard University- Black Rock Forest, 14. Hudson Highlands, 15. Indian Point, 16. Land Purchasess 17. march-South Transmission Lines, 18. Paper Recycling, 19. Springside, 20. Storm King Mountain, 21. Transportation, 22. Wallace Fund, 23. West Meets East, 24. Environmental studies, this sderies has eight subseries, 25. Exhibits, 26. Clippings, 27. Photographs, 28. Hanging Photographs, and 29. Audio-Visual oversized matierals, this series has five subseries.
The series are arranged either by subject or chronologically.
Related Collections
Hudson River Environmental Society Library
- Background Material, 1; 0.67 linear feet Boxes: 1 - 2 Folders: 1 - 19
  Documents pertaining to the formation and development of Scenic Hudson, Inc.
  By subject
  - General Information (Folder 1, Box 1)
  - Job&Project Descriptions (Folder 2, Box 1)
  - Job Descriptions, Rockefeller Foundation Internship (Folder 3, Box 1)
  - Chronology (Folder 4, Box 1)
  - Fisheries Investigations (Folder 5, Box 1)
  - Con Edison’s Proposed Hydroelectric Project, Cornwall, New York (Folder 6, Box 1)
  - Hudson River Model Society for Con Edison, 1966-1969 (Folder 7, Box 1)
  - Hydraulic Model Study - 1976 for Con Edison (Folder 8, Box 1)
  - Hudson River Advisory Council (Folder 9, Box 1)
  - By-Laws SHPC (Folder 10, Box 1)
  - Proposal (Folder 11, Box 1)
  - Initial Projects Assignments (Folder 12, Box 1)
  - Misc. (Folder 13, Box 1)
  - Marist College Seminar (Folder 14, Box 2)
  - Scenic Hudson Reorganization (Folder 15, Box 2)
  - Hudson River Conservation Society - preliminary correspondence (Folder 16, Box 2)
  - Awards, American Heritage (Folder 17, Box 2)
  - Awards, Conservation Council (Folder 18, Box 2)
  - Awards, American Motors Conservation (Folder 19, Box 2)
- Meetings, 1970-1998; 2; 1 linear foot Boxes: 3 - 5 Folders: 20 - 79
  Memos, minutes, notes, and agendas of meetings.
  Chronological
  - 10/15/1970 (Folder 20, Box 3)
  - 01/20/1971 (Folder 21, Box 3)
  - 02/18/1971 (Folder 22, Box 3)
  - 03/18/1971 (Folder 23, Box 3)
  - 04/15/1971 (Folder 24, Box 3)
  - 05/27/1971 (Folder 25, Box 3)
  - 06/24/1971 (Folder 26, Box 3)
  - 08/26/1971 (Folder 27, Box 3)
  - 10/21/1971 (Folder 28, Box 3)
  - 11/08/1971 (Folder 29, Box 3)
  - 12/16/1971 (Folder 30, Box 3)
  - 10/21/1971 (Folder 31, Box 3)
  - 01/21/1972 (Folder 32, Box 3)
  - 02/17/1972 (Folder 33, Box 3)
  - 03/16/1972 (Folder 34, Box 3)
  - 04/20/1972 (Folder 35, Box 3)
  - 05/18/1972 (Folder 36, Box 3)
  - 06/15/1972 (Folder 37, Box 3)
  - 06/29/1972 (Folder 38, Box 3)
  - 08/24/1972 (Folder 39, Box 3)
  - 09/21/1972 (Folder 40, Box 3)
  - 09/26/1972 (Folder 41, Box 3)
  - 11/16/1972 (Folder 42, Box 3)
  - 12/19/1972 (Folder 43, Box 3)
  - 1973 (Folder 44, Box 3)
  - 1974 (Folder 45, Box 3)
  - 1975 (Folder 46, Box 3)
  - 03/27/1976 (Folder 47, Box 3)
  - 02/17/1977 (Folder 48, Box 3)
  - 04/21/1977 (Folder 49, Box 3)
  - 05/19/1977 (Folder 50, Box 3)
  - 08/18/1977 (Folder 51, Box 3)
  - 11/17/1977 (Folder 52, Box 3)
  - 07/20/1978 (Folder 53, Box 3)
  - 08/17/1978 (Folder 54, Box 3)
  - 11/16/1978 (Folder 55, Box 3)
  - 06/15/1978 (Folder 56, Box 3)
  - 03/23/1978 (Folder 57, Box 3)
  - 1976 (Folder 58, Box 4)
  - 02/21/1976 - Lyndhurst Meeting (Folder 59, Box 4)
  - 1977 (Folder 60, Box 4)
  - 1978 (Folder 61, Box 4)
  - 1979 (Folder 62, Box 4)
  - Mrs. Willis Reese Executive Committee Meeting, 01/23/1997 (Folder 63, Box 4)
  - Mrs. Willis Reese Executive Committee Meeting, 03/20/1997 (Folder 64, Box 4)
  - Mrs. Willis Reese Executive Committee Meeting, 05/08/1997 (Folder 65, Box 4)
  - Mrs. Willis Reese Executive Committee Meeting, 06/24/1997 (Folder 66, Box 4)
  - Mrs. Willis Reese Executive Committee Meeting, 09/16/1997 (Folder 67, Box 4)
  - Mrs. Willis Reese Executive Committee Meeting, 10/14/1997 (Folder 68, Box 4)
  - Mrs. Willis Reese Executive Committee Meeting, 11/11/1997 (Folder 69, Box 4)
  - Mrs. Willis Reese Executive Committee Meeting, 12/11/1997 (Folder 70, Box 4)
  - Executive Director’s Report (Folder 71, Box 5)
  - Mrs. Willis Reese Executive Committee Meeting, 01/27/1998 (Folder 72, Box 5)
  - Mrs. Willis Reese Executive Committee Meeting, 03/19/1998 (Folder 73, Box 5)
  - Mrs. Willis Reese Executive Committee Meeting, 05/07/1998 (Folder 74, Box 5)
  - Mrs. Willis Reese Executive Committee Meeting, 06/23/1998 (Folder 75, Box 5)
  - Mrs. Willis Reese Executive Committee Meeting, 09/15/1998 (Folder 76, Box 5)
  - Mrs. Willis Reese Executive Committee Meeting, 10/20/1998 (Folder 77, Box 5)
  - Mrs. Willis Reese Executive Committee Meeting, 11/17/1998 (Folder 78, Box 5)
  - Mrs. Willis Reese Executive Committee Meeting, 12/15/1998 (Folder 79, Box 5)
- Legal papers, 1965-1981; 3; 3.33 linear feet Boxes: 6 - 15 Folders: 80 - 135
  Legal Documents, such as Stenographers’ Reports, Briefs, and Case Files, as well as notes and various legal correspondences.
  - Reply Brief of Sierra Club, 1976 (Folder Folder 80, Box 6)
  - Scenic Hudson vs. Federal Power Commission&Edison, etc. (Folder Folder 81, Box 6)
  - Order Denying Petitions for Rehearing, 07/14/1977 (Folder Folder 82, Box 6)
  - Legislative Effort (Folder Folder 83, Box 6)
  - Supplemental Petition at SHPC, 12/18/1973 (Folder Folder 84, Box 6)
  - Lobbying Reports, 1977-1979 (Folder Folder 85, Box 6)
  - Lobbying Reports, 1980-1981 (Folder Folder 86, Box 6)
  - Area of National Concern (Folder Folder 87, Box 6)
  - Heritage Conservation&Recreation Service (Folder Folder 88, Box 6)
  - The Catskill Center Legislation (Folder Folder 89, Box 6)
  - Hudson River Valley Commission Legislation (Folder Folder 90, Box 6)
  - Case 26974 - Comparing Nuclear&Fuel (Folder Folder 91, Box 6)
  - FPC Project # 2338, 1969-1978 (Folder Folder 92, Box 6)
  - Testimony Before the FPC - Abraham Groonman (Folder Folder 93, Box 6)
  - Testimony Before the FPC - Thomas W. Fluhr (Folder Folder 94, Box 6)
  - Testimony Before the FPC - Thomas F. Wright (Folder Folder 95, Box 6)
  - Testimony Before the FPC - Torris Eide (Folder Folder 96, Box 6)
  - Testimony Before the FPC - Fred C. Stein (Folder Folder 97, Box 6)
  - Mary Harris Bell vs. Con Edison (Folder Folder 98, Box 7)
  - H.R. 7052 - A Bill to Amend the Federal Power Act (Folder Folder 99, Box 7)
  - Case 70126: Reply Brief of Applicant Power Authority (Folder Folder 100, Box 7)
  - Statements Submitted to the Commission Public Meeting, 06/29/1965 (Folder Folder 101, Box 8)
  - Hearings (Folder Folder 102, Box 8)
  - Hearings (Folder Folder 103, Box 8)
  - Stenographers’ Report, FPC-Con Ed, pg. 680-813 (Folder Folder 104, Box 8)
  - Stenographers’ Report, FPC-Con Ed, pg. 1412-1577 (Folder Folder 105, Box 8)
  - Stenographers’ Report, FPC-Con Ed, pg. 2575-2797 (Folder Folder 106, Box 8)
  - Stenographers’ Report, FPC-Con Ed, pg. 2780-2946 (Folder Folder 107, Box 9)
  - Stenographers’ Report, FPC-Con Ed, pg. 2947-3080 (Folder Folder 108, Box 9)
  - Stenographers’ Report, FPC-Con Ed, pg. 3081-3259 (Folder Folder 109, Box 9)
  - Stenographers’ Report, FPC-Con Ed, pg. 3260-3458 (Folder Folder 110, Box 9)
  - Stenographers’ Report, FPC-Con Ed, pg. 3853-4105 (Folder Folder 111, Box 9)
  - Stenographers’ Report, FPC-Con Ed, pg. 4106-4301 (Folder Folder 112, Box 10)
  - Stenographers’ Report, FPC-Con Ed, pg. 4302-4489 (Folder Folder 113, Box 10)
  - Stenographers’ Report, FPC-Con Ed, pg. 4490-4887 (4490-4682) (Folder Folder 114, Box 10)
  - Stenographers’ Report, FPC-Con Ed, pg. 4490-4887 (4683-4887) (Folder Folder 115, Box 10)
  - Volume 1, 08/19/1974 (Folder Folder 116, Box 11)
  - Volume 2, 10/08/1974 (Folder Folder 117, Box 11)
  - Volume 3, 10/09/1974 (Folder Folder 118, Box 11)
  - Volume 4, 10/22/1974 (Folder Folder 119, Box 12)
  - Volume 6, 10/24/1974 (Folder Folder 120, Box 12)
  - Volume 6, 10/24/1974 (Folder Folder 121, Box 12)
  - Volume 7, 10/25/1974 (Folder Folder 122, Box 12)
  - (Box 12)
  - Volume 8, 10/29/1974 (Folder Folder 123, Box 13)
  - Volume 10, 10/31/1974 (Folder Folder 124, Box 13)
  - Volume 11, 11/01/1974 (Folder Folder 125, Box 13)
  - Volume 12, 11/12/1974 (Folder Folder 126, Box 13)
  - Volume 13, 11/13/1974 (Folder Folder 127, Box 14)
  - Volume 14, 11/14/1974 (Folder Folder 128, Box 14)
  - Volume 15a, 11/15/1974 (Folder Folder 129, Box 14)
  - Volume 15, 11/15/1974 (Folder Folder 130, Box 14)
  - Volume 17, 11/20/1974 (Folder Folder 131, Box 14)
  - Volume 18, 11/21/1974 (Folder Folder 132, Box 15)
  - Volume 19, 11/22/1974 (Folder Folder 133, Box 15)
  - Volume 21, 11/26/1974 (Folder Folder 134, Box 15)
  - Volume 28, 12/13/1974 (Folder Folder 135, Box 15)
- General Correspondence, 1963-1997; 4; 1.33 linear feet Boxes: 16 - 19 Folders: 136 - 173
  Letters, memos, notes, and notices to and from Scenic Hudson, Inc.
  - 1963-1966 (Folder 136, Box 16)
  - 1969-1970, 1972 (Folder 137, Box 16)
  - 1973 (Folder 138, Box 16)
  - 1974 (Folder 139, Box 16)
  - 1975 (Folder 150, Box 16)
  - 1976 Jan.-Aug. (Folder 141, Box 16)
  - 1976 Sept.-Dec. (Folder 142, Box 16)
  - 1977 Jan.-May (Folder 143, Box 16)
  - 1977 June-Dec. (Folder 144, Box 16)
  - 1978 (Folder 145, Box 16)
  - 1979 (Folder 146, Box 16)
  - 1980 (Folder 147, Box 17)
  - 1981 (Folder 148, Box 17)
  - 1982 (Folder 149, Box 17)
  - Marketing (Folder 150, Box 18)
  - Misc. PR (Folder 151, Box 18)
  - Correspondence: Charlie Murphy (Folder 152, Box 18)
  - Correspondence: Dan Capriotti (Folder 153, Box 18)
  - Mrs. Lamb, Leo Rothschild, Scott Warthin, Benjamin Frazier (Folder 154, Box 18)
  - NYSCA 1997 Challenge Grant (Folder 155, Box 18)
  - Survey of the Residents of the Hudson Valley, February 28, 1997 (Folder 156, Box 18)
  - Al Butzel’s Office, May 1957-Dec. 1975 (Folder 157, Box 18)
  - Al Butzel’s Office, Nov. 1974-April 1975 (Folder 158, Box 18)
  - Helen Sherwood&her will (Folder 159, Box 18)
  - Correspondence: Charles Komanoff (Folder 160, Box 18)
  - Correspondence: congress, senate, etc. (Folder 161, Box 18)
  - Norman, Lawrence,&Richard Inc. (Folder 162, Box 19)
  - Requests for Info. (Folder 163, Box 19)
  - Memos to Board, 1970&undated (Folder 164, Box 19)
  - Memos to Board, 1971 (Folder 165, Box 19)
  - Memos to Board, 1972 (Folder 166, Box 19)
  - Memos&Notices, 2/71 (Folder 167, Box 19)
  - Memos&Notices, 3/71 (Folder 168, Box 19)
  - Memos&Notices, 6/71 (Folder 169, Box 19)
  - Memos&Notices, 7/71 (Folder 170, Box 19)
  - Memos&Notices, 8/71 (Folder 171, Box 19)
  - Memos&Notices, 9/71 (Folder 172, Box 19)
  - Correspondence: Ferma Print (Folder 173, Box 19)
- Printed Material, 1964-2000; 5; 8.67 linear foot Boxes: 20 - 46 Folders: 174 - 544
  Pamphlets, brochures, magazines, Scenic Hudson Bulletins, Scenic Hudson News, publications, books, research, reports, and stationary relating to Scenic Hudson, Inc. and the Hudson River Valley.
  Divided into 10 subseries, seperated by subject
  - Environmental Guide Books, 5.1
    Guide Books
    - The Hudson River Guide (Folder 174, Box 20)
    - Building a Metropolitan Greensward (Folder 175, Box 20)
    - MHD Power Generation (Folder 176, Box 20)
    - Environmental Group Directory Region II, 1976 (Folder 177, Box 20)
    - Directions Through Region II (Folder 178, Box 20)
    - The Case for a Simpler Lifestyle (Folder 179, Box 20)
    - National Environmental Research Center/Program Directory (Folder 180, Box 20)
    - The Hudson Archeological Sites (Folder 181, Box 20)
    - The Federal Environmental Monitoring Directory (Folder 182, Box 20)
    - American Forests (Folder 183, Box 20)
    - How to Harness sun power and avoid pollution (Folder 184, Box 20)
  - Environmental Reports, 5.2
    Reports on the Hudson River, progress reports, the Hudson River Valley, and power; Electronic Weekly; Electric Weekly October 1971-December 1972
    - The Hudson Riverfront Commerce (Folder 185, Box 21)
    - The Hudson River Lighthouses (Folder 186, Box 21)
    - Con Edison 1971 Annual Report (Folder 187, Box 21)
    - A Survey of Rivers In the Adirondack Physiographic Province to Identify Potential National Wild and Scenic Study Rivers (Folder 188, Box 21)
    - Summary Report of the Hudson River Valley Commission (Folder 189, Box 21)
    - ’67-’68 progress report, department of air resources, N.Y.C. (Folder 190, Box 21)
    - The Nuclear Industry 1970 (Folder 191, Box 21)
    - Environmental Priorities for New York City, Interium Report 1974.1984 (Folder 192, Box 21)
    - Hudson River Valley Commission, Annual Report 1968 (Folder 193, Box 21)
    - Electric Power and the Environment (Folder 194, Box 21)
    - Regional Tourism Strategy (Folder 195, Box 21)
    - Ecological Forestry for the Douglas Fir Region (Folder 196, Box 21)
    - The Great Environmental Debate and the Power Industry (Folder 197, Box 21)
    - The Hudson Population (Folder 198, Box 21)
    - (Folder 199, Box 22)
    - Air Pollution in New York City (Folder 200, Box 23)
    - Pollution of the Hudson River and its Tributaries (Folder 201, Box 23)
    - University Curricula in the Marine Sciences and Related Fields (Folder 202, Box 23)
    - Draft Environmental impact Statement (Folder 203, Box 23)
    - Anatomy of an Environment: Final Report (Folder 204, Box 23)
    - The Hudson Water Resources (Folder 205, Box 23)
    - Environmental Science and Technology (Folder 206, Box 23)
    - New England River Basins Commission, 1973 Annual Repot (Folder 207, Box 23)
    - Global Status of Mangrove Ecosystems (Folder 208, Box 23)
    - Coastal State Reports (Folder 209, Box 23)
    - Misc. Reports (Folder 210, Box 23)
  - Sub Series 5.3: Environmental Research, 5.3
    American Heritage, NYC, transportation, and engineering; Energy, railroads, water conservation, resource development; Power plants, air quality, relationship between mankind and the environment
    - American Heritage (Folder 211, Box 24)
    - Environmental quality and New York City (Folder 212, Box 24)
    - Statewide Comprehensive Outdoor Recreation Plan (Folder 213, Box 24)
    - Maintaining Mobility, The Plan and Program for Regional Transportation Through 2000 (Folder 214, Box 24)
    - Engineering for Resolution of the Enerby Environment Dilemma (Folder 215, Box 24)
    - Sectorial Planning Guidelines for Environmental Management (Folder 216, Box 25)
    - Energy and the Environment, Electric Power (Folder 217, Box 25)
    - The Environmental Volunteer (Folder 218, Box 25)
    - United States National Viewpoint Statement on the Environment (Folder 219, Box 25)
    - Historic Resources (Folder 220, Box 25)
    - Man and his urban Environment (Folder 221, Box 25)
    - Between the Railroad and the River (Folder 222, Box 25)
    - Guidelines for Preparation and Environmental Impact Evaluations (Folder 223, Box 25)
    - Coastal Resource Development and Management Needs of Developing Countries (Folder 224, Box 25)
    - Coastal Zone Management: An annotated bibliography (Folder 225, Box 25)
    - Lectures on Water Conservation (Folder 226, Box 25)
    - Background information relating to environmental guidelines for zones in gulf of Thailand (Folder 227, Box 25)
    - (Box 25)
    - Power Plant Performance (Folder 228, Box 26)
    - How to Stop the Corporate Polluters and Make Money Doing it (Folder 229, Box 26)
    - Transactions of the New York Academy of Sciences (Folder 230, Box 26)
    - Ecological Aspects of Development in the Humid Tropics (Folder 231, Box 26)
    - Hudson River Colloquium (Folder 232, Box 26)
    - A Guide to the Air Quality Act of 1967 (Folder 233, Box 26)
    - How to Challenge your Local Electric Utility (Folder 234, Box 26)
    - Natural Gas: Price Regulation V. Supply (Folder 235, Box 26)
    - Action for Clean Waters (Folder 236, Box 26)
    - The New York Pollution Survival Kit (Folder 237, Box 26)
    - Electric Power Transmission and the Environment (Folder 238, Box 26)
    - Man, Land, and Sea (Folder 239, Box 26)
    - Misc. Research (Folder 240, Box 26)
  - Books, 5.4
    Environmental books
    - The Hudson River and its Painters (Paper Back) (Folder 241, Box 27)
    - The Hudson River and its Painters (Paper Back) (Folder 242, Box 27)
    - The Hudson River and its Painters (Hard Cover) (Folder 243, Box 27)
    - The Hudson River and its Painters (Hard Cover) (Folder 244, Box 27)
    - Hudson River Valley Commission (Folder 245, Box 27)
    - The Master Plan for the New York State Capitol (Folder 246, Box 27)
  - Scenic Hudson News, 1970-2000; 5.5
    Updates, Preservation Conference Material
    - Scenic Hudson News, 1971 (Folder 247, Box 28)
    - Scenic Hudson News, May-June 1972 (Folder 248, Box 28)
    - Scenic Hudson News, Fall 1972 (Folder 249, Box 28)
    - Scenic Hudson News, 1972 (Folder 250, Box 28)
    - Scenic Hudson News, Fall 1973 (Folder 251, Box 28)
    - Scenic Hudson News, Spring 1974 (Folder 252, Box 28)
    - Scenic Hudson News, 1974 Special Edition (Folder 253, Box 28)
    - Scenic Hudson News, 1975 (Folder 254, Box 28)
    - Scenic Hudson News, Autumn 1975 (Folder 255, Box 28)
    - Scenic Hudson News, Spring 1976 (Folder 256, Box 28)
    - Scenic Hudson News, Fall 1976 (Folder 257, Box 28)
    - Scenic Hudson News, Spring 1977 (Folder 258, Box 28)
    - Scenic Hudson News, Fall 1977 (Folder 259, Box 28)
    - Scenic Hudson News, Spring 1978 (Folder 260, Box 28)
    - Scenic Hudson News, Fall 1978 (Folder 261, Box 28)
    - Scenic Hudson News, Spring 1979 (Folder 262, Box 28)
    - Scenic Hudson News, Fall, 1979 (Folder 263, Box 28)
    - Scenic Hudson News, 1980 (Folder 264, Box 28)
    - Scenic Hudson News, Spring 1981 (Folder 265, Box 28)
    - Scenic Hudson News, Spring 1982 (Folder 266, Box 28)
    - Scenic Hudson News, Fall 1982 (Folder 267, Box 28)
    - Scenic Hudson News, Spring 1983 (Folder 268, Box 28)
    - Scenic Hudson News, Fall 1983 (Folder 269, Box 28)
    - Scenic Hudson News, 1986 (Folder 270, Box 28)
    - Scenic Hudson Report, Conservation Conference, 1969 (Folder 271, Box 28)
    - Scenic Hudson, Preservation Conference (Folder 272, Box 28)
    - Scenic Hudson News Update (Folder 273, Box 28)
    - Scenic Hudson News, Fall 1991 (Folder 274, Box 29)
    - Scenic Hudson News, Fall 1992 (Folder 275, Box 29)
    - Scenic Hudson News, Winter 1992 (Folder 276, Box 29)
    - Scenic Hudson News, 1993 (Folder 277, Box 29)
    - Scenic Hudson News, 1994 (Folder 278, Box 29)
    - Scenic Hudson News, Summer 1995 (Folder 279, Box 29)
    - Scenic Hudson News, Winter 1995 (Folder 280, Box 29)
    - Scenic Hudson News, Spring 1996 (Folder 281, Box 29)
    - Scenic Hudson News, Winter 1996 (Folder 282, Box 29)
    - Scenic Hudson News, Fall 1997 (Folder 283, Box 29)
    - Scenic Hudson News, Spring and Summer, 1998 (Folder 284, Box 29)
    - Scenic Hudson News, Fall 1998 (Folder 285, Box 29)
    - Scenic Hudson News, Spring and Summer 1999 (Folder 286, Box 29)
    - Scenic Hudson News, Spring and Summer 2000 (Folder 287, Box 29)
    - Scenic Hudson News, Winter/Spring and Summer 2001 (Folder 288, Box 29)
    - Scenic Hudson News, Winter/Spring 2002 (Folder 289, Box 29)
  - Scenic Hudson Inc. Publications and Reports, 1965-2000; 5.6
    Annual Reports; Scenic Hudson Inc. Publications and Reports; Scenic Hudson Publications; Scenic Hudson Stationary/Original Layouts/Graphics
    - Annual Report, 1981 (Folder 290, Box 30)
    - Annual Report, 1982 (Folder 291, Box 30)
    - Annual Report, 1983 (Folder 292, Box 30)
    - Annual Report, 1984 (Folder 293, Box 30)
    - Annual Report, 1985 (Folder 294, Box 30)
    - Annual Report, 1986 (Folder 295, Box 30)
    - Annual Report, 1987-88 (Folder 296, Box 30)
    - Annual Report, 1989 (Folder 297, Box 30)
    - Annual Report, 1990 (Folder 298, Box 30)
    - Annual Report, 1990-91 (Folder 299, Box 30)
    - Annual Report, 1991-92 (Folder 300, Box 30)
    - Annual Report, 1992-93 (Folder 301, Box 30)
    - nnual Report, 1993-94 (Folder 302, Box 30)
    - Annual Report, 1994-95 (Folder 303, Box 30)
    - Annual Report, 1995-96 (Folder 304, Box 30)
    - Annual Report, 1996-97 (Folder 305, Box 30)
    - Annual Report, 1997-98 (Folder 306, Box 30)
    - Annual Report, 1999 (Folder 307, Box 30)
    - Annual Report, 2000 (Folder 308, Box 30)
    - Scenic Hudson Bulletin #1/ 03/09/1965 (Folder 309, Box 31)
    - Scenic Hudson Bulletin #2, 03/17/1965 (Folder 310, Box 31)
    - Scenic Hudson Bulletin #3,11/18/9165 (Folder 311, Box 31)
    - Scenic Hudson Bulletin #4, 04/14/1965 (Folder 312, Box 31)
    - Scenic Hudson Bulletin #6 05/19/1965 (Folder 313, Box 31)
    - Scenic Hudson Bulletin #7, 06/11/1965 (Folder 314, Box 31)
    - Scenic Hudson Bulletin # 8, 07/19/1965 (Folder 315, Box 31)
    - Scenic Hudson Bulletin #9, 08/06/1965 (Folder 316, Box 31)
    - Scenic Hudson Bulletin #11, 10/22/1965 (Folder 317, Box 31)
    - Scenic Hudson Bulletin #12, 02/14/1966 (Folder 318, Box 31)
    - Scenic Hudson Bulletin #13, 03/13/1966 (Folder 319, Box 31)
    - Scenic Hudson Bulletin #14 03/31/1966 (Folder 320, Box 31)